goldspot.com 2014-11-24

# Fountain Pens - Discount on Waterman, Parker, Cross, Pelikan, Montegrappa, Acme and fine writing pens. - Goldspot

Respecting and protecting your privacy is very important to Goldspot. We recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner. Below we describe why we gather customer and member information, what information we collect, how we collect it, what we use the information for and how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information. This Privacy Policy is part of the Terms of Use, which governs your use of Goldspot.com. 

**Why do we gather information?**  
We gather personal information to allow us to process your orders, to provide an enhanced and more personalized shopping experience and to inform you of special offers and discounts. 

**What information do we gather?**  
When you order from our Web site, we may collect the following information: your name, telephone number, email address, billing information (credit card number, expiration date and billing address), products purchased, and any relevant promotion code. 

**How we use the information we collect about you.**  
We use information we collect from you to process your orders, to provide an enhanced and more personalized shopping experience and to inform you and your gift recipients of offers and discounts from Goldspot.com or other sites and companies that we own. We do not make you or your gift recipient's mailing address or email addresses available to third parties.

**Email**  
When you submit feedback or questions via e-mail, or contact us for information about our website, we will request your name and e-mail address. We use this information solely to respond to your inquiries. 

Our email newsletters are intended to keep users informed of new products, gifts, and special features that are available. Our policy is to send our email announcements or newsletters only to those who request this when registering. If you receive an email and want to be removed from the email list, we provide instructions on how to unsubscribe so that you will not receive any other messages from Goldspot.com in the future.

**Your Security**  
Our Web site encrypts your credit card number prior to transmission over the Internet using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption technology. This technology works best when the site is viewed using an internet browser like Microsoft Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, or Safari.

However, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Although we make reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, we cannot warrant the security of information you transmit to us.

**Your Consent and Changes to this Policy**   
Subject to the above provisions, by using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by us and the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time and we will post those changes so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it. In addition, if you would like prior notice of changes to the Privacy Policy or Terms of Use, email us at gshelp@goldspot.com from the email address to which you would like notice sent. By using Goldspot.com, after such changes and posting, you agree to be legally bound and to abide by the changes and other provisions contained in the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.
